<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: annoyances | Sol Net]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.hellocalvin.com/blog/categories/annoyances/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.hellocalvin.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-18T00:43:13-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.hellocalvin.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[random things that could be better]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.hellocalvin.com/2014/02/14/random-things-that-could-be-better/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-14T01:07:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.hellocalvin.com/2014/02/14/random-things-that-could-be-better</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://weknowmemes.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/rage-guy-original.png"></p>

<p>So I was thinking today...well, I like to think that I think everyday, but in this case...my thinking has had a backlog of sorts.  I feel like I need to write this out as a sort of therapy to release my pressure valve.</p>

<p>Life is great for me right now, but ...</p>

<p>Certain things that either have been annoying me or could be better have been bubbling up, but these 'things' have no particular distinction of being related, save for them being annoying or have the potential to be better...</p>

<!-- more -->


<h3>Why doesn't Chick-fil-a have a self-serve soda dispenser like everyone else?</h3>

<p>You could probably make a good business case for why not:</p>

<ul>
<li>More efficient spending on soda syrup because less people will make effort to get refill</li>
<li>More interaction with customers face-to-face</li>
<li>Less mess to clean up</li>
</ul>


<p>Things that annoy me about it:</p>

<ul>
<li>Giant ice cubes fill the cup, leaving about 2.5 gulps of drink</li>
<li>I like diet coke, but everyone always hears, 'coke'</li>
<li>Having to wait a long time when I'm thirsty</li>
</ul>


<p>The long and short of it is basically that....I've been conditioned with every other fast food place that I can self serve and create my own concoction (sometimes I put fruit punch with my diet coke....or have sprite with rootbeer).  I value this.</p>

<p>I also get annoyed when I am going through the drive thru getting ready to go on a long trip, only to run out of my caffeinated soda 3 blocks away from leaving the place.</p>

<p>The problem I see:</p>

<p> When you have to go back to get a refill, it clogs up the process and the area in which others are waiting to be served...people bump each other, children going up for refills get overlooked, parents going up on behalf of more than a few are left waiting in the sidelines...it just seems to get messy, which is probably why I never feel relaxed when dining in Chick-fil-a...there just seems to be so much traffic.</p>

<h3>Amazon, you could do better with your HD purchases in Instant Video and probably, in theory, get more people to convert from Standard</h3>

<p> I probably spend way more money than I should at Amazon, especially with Instant Video, but I don't feel like Im alone in this as they make it amazingly easy to purchase their products, but the thing about it is....</p>

<p> I always balk at buying HD video as opposed to the standard offering that is right beside it, and when I say balk, I mean I usually never buy the HD...but sometimes...especially if I were to get a larger tv or brand new HD flatscreen, I would consider purchasing the HD version of something I already bought.....but I don't want to have 2 copies of the same thing.  It 'feels' like I would be wasting my money.</p>

<p> So if I were Amazon...and I am not, but if I were, and I wanted to sell more HD Instant video, I would probably consider providing something like an upgrade option if the customer already owns the Standard format version.  So if I owned Pawn Stars (yes I do), and I bought the standard for $1.99....then it might make sense to allow the customer to 'upgrade' to the HD format for only a dollar more, instead of paying the full $2.99.  Doesn't that make a lot more sense?</p>

<p> It just seems like a big missed opportunity if you wanted to convert more people to HD instant video. #amiright</p>

<h3>I really wish more people used primary sources</h3>

<p> Facebook is probably the impetus for this one, but seriously....question the information and where it came from!</p>

<p> A lot of people like to call our social media a 'fire-hose' or something to the effect of a large ocean or web or something, but the fact is: A METRIC ASS-TON OF INFORMATION IS BLASTED INTO YOUR EYEBALLS, EARS...all the time!</p>

<p> my favorite quote:</p>

<p> <blockquote>What information consumes is rather obvious: it consumes the attention of its recipients. Hence a wealth of information creates a poverty of attention, and a need to allocate that attention efficiently among the overabundance of information sources that might consume it. - Herbert Simon</blockquote></p>

<p> I suppose what I'm really getting at is not totally related to using primary sources, but evaluating the information you post.</p>

<p> To me, primary sources are the highest quality information you can get.  My opinions on my blog are a primary source, peer-reviewed scientific articles are usually primary sources, taking a picture at an event is a primary source.</p>

<h3>Shared Facebook accounts</h3>

<p>I think the theme here is honesty, but moreso it's goes back to primary sources.  I know some people do shared accounts as a gesture of oneness with their significant other, but I don't really see the benefit.</p>

<p>I love my wife, and we are one couple, one unity under God, but we still are individuals, and when I speak, I may not be speaking for her and I want her to speak for herself.</p>

<p>It ultimately seems deceiving because I rarely know who is speaking from the account, and it's just weird!</p>

<h3>Whatevs, right</h3>

<p>Who cares, right?  Really though, there are so many day to day things that could be better, could be worse.  I just thought to highlight a few of them here.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
