<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: recipe | Sol Net]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/blog/categories/recipe/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-04T15:18:00-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.calvin.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[just flour and water]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/2013/08/01/just-flour-and-water/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-01T00:02:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.calvin.io/2013/08/01/just-flour-and-water</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/calweb/9411148263/" title="Homemade pasta by Calweb, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2822/9411148263_2f75f2e275.jpg" width="500" height="500" alt="Homemade pasta"></a></p>

<p>It's funny how almost a year goes by and no updates...so I thought to put something up here just to go through the motions of actually updating my blog....</p>

<p>Have you ever made homemade glue when you were younger?  You know...the flour and water variety?</p>

<p>Those who know me, also know that I like cooking, but I tend to just 'wing it'...and add things to a recipe as I taste, which is probably why I never was that great at baking or making candy.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The thing is, I've had a recent revelation on something awesome I can cook all the time, and it's really easy!!</p>

<p>It's called pasta!  Just flour and water, or flour and eggs, or flour and eggs and tomato paste.</p>

<p>And to make it really easy, it's a 2:1 ratio, or thereabouts!  I mean, you mix until it turns into a dough ball, then you beat it up until it's all stretchy!</p>

<p>You can use plain flour or a blend of both semolina and regular, bleached flour in a 1:1 ratio.</p>

<p>Here's my recipe that I stole of some site, or off of some packaging that works great!</p>

<h3>Calvin's Copied Pasta Recipe:</h3>

<ul>
    <li>1 cup Red Mill Brand Semolina flour</li>
    <li>1 cup All Purpose flour</li>
    <li> 1 teaspoon salt</li>
    <li>1 cup (roughly) water</li>
    <li>1 tablespoon Olive Oil</li>
</ul>


<h3>Directions:</h3>

<ol>
    <li>Sift or mix flour(s) with salt until well mixed and fluffy</li>
    <li>Make pyramid on clean surface and then make volcano hold in middle (for wet ingredients)</li>
    <li>Pour water or lightly beaten eggs and olive oil into volcano crater in middle</li>
    <li>Carefully cave in and mix volcano walls into wet center, slowly using hands (TIP: better less liquid first, then add as needed)</li>
    <li>Once dough sticks together, but not to your fingers, start making into ball and kneading</li>
    <li>Knead for at least 15 minutes either by hand or mixer with dough hook until dough is smooth and elastic (TIP: this is important as it will be brittle if not kneaded enough)</li>
    <li>Let dough rest for at least 20 minutes</li>
    <li>Begin making pasta!</li>
</ol>


<p>Seeing as how my wife is Italian, I'm sure to impress my in-laws next time they come over for dinner! :)</p>

<p>I made this recipe with just water for cavatelli's (sorry, no picture), but it was pretty time intensive as you need to pinch off tiny balls and thumb press and stretch, which takes a while, but they were Delicious!!!
The picture above shows the finished product with spaghetti noodles made with eggs and run through a pasta cutter.</p>

<p>Delish!  Who would've thought that pasta would be so easy to make!  I now have started making this at least once a week, well, for the past 2 weeks....but I see this happening regularly.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
