<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[undefined - Calvin Webster]]></title><description><![CDATA[My space for space]]></description><link>http://calweb.github.io/</link><generator>Ghost</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 21:02:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://calweb.github.io/tag/undefined/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Random things that could be better]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://weknowmemes.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/rage-guy-original.png" alt=""></p>
<p>So I was thinking today&#8230;well, I like to think that I think everyday, but in this case&#8230;my thinking has had a backlog of sorts.  I feel like I need to write this out as a sort of therapy to release my pressure valve.</p>
<p>Life is great for me right now, but &#8230;</p>
<p>Certain things that either have been annoying me or could be better have been bubbling up, but these &#8216;things&#8217; have no particular distinction of being related, save for them being annoying or have the potential to be better&#8230;</p>
<h3 id="why-doesn-t-chick-fil-a-have-a-self-serve-soda-dispenser-like-everyone-else-">Why doesn&#39;t Chick-fil-a have a self-serve soda dispenser like everyone else?</h3>
<p>You could probably make a good business case for why not:</p>
<ul>
<li>More efficient spending on soda syrup because less people will make effort to get refill</li>
<li>More interaction with customers face-to-face</li>
<li>Less mess to clean up</li>
</ul>
<p>Things that annoy me about it:</p>
<ul>
<li>Giant ice cubes fill the cup, leaving about 2.5 gulps of drink</li>
<li>I like diet coke, but everyone always hears, &#8216;coke&#8217;</li>
<li>Having to wait a long time when I&#8217;m thirsty</li>
</ul>
<p>The long and short of it is basically that&#8230;.I&#8217;ve been conditioned with every other fast food place that I can self serve and create my own concoction (sometimes I put fruit punch with my diet coke&#8230;.or have sprite with rootbeer).  I value this.</p>
<p>I also get annoyed when I am going through the drive thru getting ready to go on a long trip, only to run out of my caffeinated soda 3 blocks away from leaving the place.</p>
<p>The problem I see:</p>
<p> When you have to go back to get a refill, it clogs up the process and the area in which others are waiting to be served&#8230;people bump each other, children going up for refills get overlooked, parents going up on behalf of more than a few are left waiting in the sidelines&#8230;it just seems to get messy, which is probably why I never feel relaxed when dining in Chick-fil-a&#8230;there just seems to be so much traffic.</p>
<h3 id="amazon-you-could-do-better-with-your-hd-purchases-in-instant-video-and-probably-in-theory-get-more-people-to-convert-from-standard">Amazon, you could do better with your HD purchases in Instant Video and probably, in theory, get more people to convert from Standard</h3>
<p> I probably spend way more money than I should at Amazon, especially with Instant Video, but I don&#8217;t feel like Im alone in this as they make it amazingly easy to purchase their products, but the thing about it is&#8230;.</p>
<p> I always balk at buying HD video as opposed to the standard offering that is right beside it, and when I say balk, I mean I usually never buy the HD&#8230;but sometimes&#8230;especially if I were to get a larger tv or brand new HD flatscreen, I would consider purchasing the HD version of something I already bought&#8230;..but I don&#8217;t want to have 2 copies of the same thing.  It &#8216;feels&#8217; like I would be wasting my money.</p>
<p> So if I were Amazon&#8230;and I am not, but if I were, and I wanted to sell more HD Instant video, I would probably consider providing something like an upgrade option if the customer already owns the Standard format version.  So if I owned Pawn Stars (yes I do), and I bought the standard for $1.99&#8230;.then it might make sense to allow the customer to &#8216;upgrade&#8217; to the HD format for only a dollar more, instead of paying the full $2.99.  Doesn&#8217;t that make a lot more sense?</p>
<p> It just seems like a big missed opportunity if you wanted to convert more people to HD instant video. #amiright</p>
<h3 id="i-really-wish-more-people-used-primary-sources">I really wish more people used primary sources</h3>
<p> Facebook is probably the impetus for this one, but seriously&#8230;.question the information and where it came from!</p>
<p> A lot of people like to call our social media a &#8216;fire-hose&#8217; or something to the effect of a large ocean or web or something, but the fact is: A METRIC ASS-TON OF INFORMATION IS BLASTED INTO YOUR EYEBALLS, EARS&#8230;all the time!</p>
<p> my favorite quote:</p>
 <blockquote>What information consumes is rather obvious: it consumes the attention of its recipients. Hence a wealth of information creates a poverty of attention, and a need to allocate that attention efficiently among the overabundance of information sources that might consume it. - Herbert Simon</blockquote>

<p> I suppose what I&#8217;m really getting at is not totally related to using primary sources, but evaluating the information you post.</p>
<p> To me, primary sources are the highest quality information you can get.  My opinions on my blog are a primary source, peer-reviewed scientific articles are usually primary sources, taking a picture at an event is a primary source.</p>
<p> Here&#8217;s a great example that I&#8217;ve seen in my feed a few times: <a href="http://www.theepochtimes.com/n3/513771-girl-killed-herself-live-on-cam-just-after-dad-husband-seen-her-while-doing-this-a-facebook-scam/">http://www.theepochtimes.com/n3/513771-girl-killed-herself-live-on-cam-just-after-dad-husband-seen-her-while-doing-this-a-facebook-scam/</a></p>
<h3 id="shared-facebook-accounts">Shared Facebook accounts</h3>
<p>I think the theme here is honesty, but moreso it&#8217;s goes back to primary sources.  I know some people do shared accounts as a gesture of oneness with their significant other, but I don&#8217;t really see the benefit.</p>
<p>I love my wife, and we are one couple, one unity under God, but we still are individuals, and when I speak, I may not be speaking for her and I want her to speak for herself.</p>
<p>It ultimately seems deceiving because I rarely know who is speaking from the account, and it&#8217;s just weird!</p>
<h3 id="whatevs-right">Whatevs, right</h3>
<p>Who cares, right?  Really though, there are so many day to day things that could be better, could be worse.  I just thought to highlight a few of them here.</p>
]]></description><link>/2014/02/14/random-things-that-could-be-better.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2014/02/14/random-things-that-could-be-better.html</guid><category><![CDATA[random]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 15:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[More of a man...]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://farm7.staticflickr.com/6112/6329588043_3ccafd063f.jpg" alt="">
It&#8217;s been close to a year that I married my best friend and the person that inspires me everyday to be a better person.
Nearly 5 years ago I packed all my stuff up and moved to Charleston to find better opportunities both for life in general and to further my career in the world of web/software development.</p>
<p>I can honestly say that on all fronts, I couldn&#8217;t be in a better position than I am now.</p>
<p>I married and became best friends with an amazing women, I have a baby on the way (less than 5wks now)&#8230;and I work at one of the best software development shops in SC.</p>
<!--more-->
<p><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7127/7771573350_41ed348f20_o.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>Personally and professionally, I&#8217;m loving life.  And with the upcoming birth of our first child, I&#8217;ve been reflecting a lot on where I&#8217;ve been and where I want to be.</p>
<p>I find that I&#8217;ve been spending a lot of time worrying about how I will be as a father and will I be able to keep the pace with the demands of a new child.  I&#8217;ve let myself go health-wise and have become &#8216;more of a man&#8217; from not paying attention to what I eat and the exercise I need to be healthy.  This, as I&#8217;m starting to realize, needs to change.</p>
<p>Changing these habits of eating and now exercising has been hard because I&#8217;ve been so unbalanced in my daily life, neglecting to really balance my personal needs.</p>
<p>I am aiming to change these bad habits and achieve more balance by honestly carving out time everyday to spend being active, whether it be a hike, the gym, or a fierce game of raquetball.</p>
<p>Time has been flying by and it&#8217;s time for me to start making sure I will be around for a while!</p>
]]></description><link>/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot.html</guid><category><![CDATA[reflection]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mobile Hackathon]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.sparcedge.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/hackathon-2012.png" alt="">
It&#8217;s about to get real folks!</p>
<p>I&#8217;m really excited to say that doing the <a href="http://hackathon.sparcedge.com">Sparc mobile hackathon</a> will satisfy another goal of mine to become a better developer as well as learning mobile development.</p>
<p>I won&#8217;t be doing it on my own, but have 2 pretty awesome and super experienced devs, Adam Mack and Beth Bradshaw.  Together we are the Ninjaneers!</p>
<p>Not only will we be having some awesome times pushing our knowledge to new heights, but we will be joining many other awesome developers in the cause.</p>
<!--more-->
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/6wiv3jOaZ5w" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>Being a UI Developer, I sometimes feel pretty intimidated when I start diving into the deeper layers of software development, and although I&#8217;ve made it this far in my career, I always feel somewhat lacking in my knowledge and skill and feel like it&#8217;s something that I always want to improve upon.  Thankfully, I will be teaming with Adam and Beth as I both look up to them and hope that their ninja skills rubb off on me.</p>
<p>There are only a few remaining items left to figure out before the hackathon begins&#8230;and that would be our ninjaneer uniforms and whether or not we are going to go native and use objective c or use Apache Cordova/Phonegap.</p>
<p>Seeing as how everyday I pretty much live in javascript, I&#8217;m inclined to want to use a framework, but both Adam and Beth are seasoned programmers in Java and C, so it would probably make sense for them to want to code native.</p>
<p>They have both showed interest in using framework like Cordova, so I&#8217;m a little excited, but also am a little curious about writing a native app too.</p>
<p>I guess we will see as we&#8217;re going to start doing our coding workouts together to hopefully warm up and be in &#8216;shape&#8217; for the event.</p>
<p>Some of the things we&#8217;ll be practicing:</p>
<ul>
<li>Accessing the device&#8217;s hardware (eg. camera, gps/location, gyro/vibrate)</li>
<li>Using the local data storage</li>
<li>Consuming data via web services</li>
<li>User Interface and Orientation</li>
</ul>
<p>We only have a few weeks left so it&#8217;s a tall order, but if we can just scratch the surface, I think we&#8217;ll be in good shape!</p>
<p>The cool thing about using a framework, is if we have time, we could potentially port it to other devices, like Android and Windows Phone :)</p>
<p>So here&#8217;s to some awesomeness going down!
</div></p>
]]></description><link>/2012/08/09/mobile-hackathon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/08/09/mobile-hackathon.html</guid><category><![CDATA[chstech]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[... I'm blogging again]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="excited-to-start-again-and-chasing-unicorns">excited to start again and chasing unicorns</h2>
<p><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8425/7734843740_4a1e70df20_n.jpg" alt="Chasing Unicorns"></p>
<p>So I&#8217;ve been on hiatus from blogging and haven&#8217;t really done it for the past few years, but I feel like lately I have a lot more to say.</p>
<p>Just in the past year I&#8217;ve gone through a lot of transformations from being a husband, and now (soon to be), father.  This is so amazing to me and I&#8217;d like to share.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve also made a lot of new friends and have been pushing my development knowledge to new levels, mostly due to my work at SPARC and the amazing coworkers I have there.</p>
<p>Stay tuned as I begin documenting my adventures!</p>
]]></description><link>/2012/08/08/and-dot-dot-dot-im-blogging-again.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/08/08/and-dot-dot-dot-im-blogging-again.html</guid><category><![CDATA[meta]]></category><category><![CDATA[random]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[I was smart all my life until...]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>&#8230;you realize you&#8217;ve been in a bubble.  As most of my friends know, I&#8217;ve started a new job at <a href="http://www.sparcedge.com">SPARC</a>, a local software dev firm&#8230;but everytime I go into work, I feel like a little baby crawling on the floor or pooping in my pants!</p>
<p>From evented javascript design to being on the front lines of enterprise app development, there&#8217;s a lot to learn.  The people are all amazing, humble, and so extremely talented that it bends my perception of what I thought I knew.  Exaggeration aside, I am excited to learn and grow in this space and hope that I too can become proficient enough to be &#8216;smart&#8217;&#8230;.. this is some additions</p>
]]></description><link>/2011/08/11/i-was-smart-all-my-life-until.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2011/08/11/i-was-smart-all-my-life-until.html</guid><category><![CDATA[random]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>