<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: acheivements | Sol Net]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/blog/categories/acheivements/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-04T15:18:00-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.calvin.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's a boy - Meet Luca Alexander Webster]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/2012/11/16/its-a-boy-meet-luca-alexander-webster/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-16T21:57:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.calvin.io/2012/11/16/its-a-boy-meet-luca-alexander-webster</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="640" height="360" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Tkl44xazDYI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>It's official!  We have (well, have had now for 2 1/2 months) a beautiful baby boy named Luca Alexander Webster, weighing in at 6lbs 12oz.</p>

<p>Needless to say things have stayed busy, especially for Anne Marie, but I'm so excited to be a father and ready to fill out my new role.  In the video above, he is less than an hour old and recovering from being intubated as he was not breathing initially when he came out.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img class="left" src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8066/8191478409_fdebb0feb8.jpg"></p>

<p>The time has flown by!  What is really cool is that I'm finding he has a cute little personality and soooo many facial expressions. All the joys people mention when having a new little one are true, and it's hard to describe how awesome it really is to hold your own, your little one.</p>

<p>Besides having a lot of reflux, he sleeps really well and is a playful baby. He's not really cooing yet, but he smiles and acts like he is riding a bicycle if you lay him flat.  He defnitely will be an active child!</p>

<p>I can't wait to start documenting more as he grows and grows.</p>

<p>I'm finding that I am thinking about things that didn't really matter to me before like what are the nearest schools or what am I doing to be ready for when he walks....or even what could he pull out of the walls that may hurt him.  Are there schools nearby that will be a good fit? Do we want to do Montessori?  Who will he be when he grows up?  Will he like who I am as a person?</p>

<p>I know some of that is a little silly, but still, its like my life got so much bigger (in a really good way)...and I want to make sure I make as much room and prepare as much as I can so I can allow as much growth, love, and happiness as possible.</p>

<p>The little guy is amazing and I can't wait for all of my friends and family to meet him!</p>

<p>Here he is as a Ninja on Halloween:</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8463/8143704874_5b6f6c8f07.jpg"></p>

<p>And his angry face when he wants to be held:</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8070/8198046318_87cf556c8f.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[more of a man...]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.calvin.io/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-13T01:06:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.calvin.io/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://farm7.staticflickr.com/6112/6329588043_3ccafd063f.jpg"></p>

<p>It's been close to a year that I married my best friend and the person that inspires me everyday to be a better person.
Nearly 5 years ago I packed all my stuff up and moved to Charleston to find better opportunities both for life in general and to further my career in the world of web/software development.</p>

<p>I can honestly say that on all fronts, I couldn't be in a better position than I am now.</p>

<p>I married and became best friends with an amazing women, I have a baby on the way (less than 5wks now)...and I work at one of the best software development shops in SC.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7127/7771573350_41ed348f20_o.jpg"></p>

<p>Personally and professionally, I'm loving life.  And with the upcoming birth of our first child, I've been reflecting a lot on where I've been and where I want to be.</p>

<p>I find that I've been spending a lot of time worrying about how I will be as a father and will I be able to keep the pace with the demands of a new child.  I've let myself go health-wise and have become 'more of a man' from not paying attention to what I eat and the exercise I need to be healthy.  This, as I'm starting to realize, needs to change.</p>

<p>Changing these habits of eating and now exercising has been hard because I've been so unbalanced in my daily life, neglecting to really balance my personal needs.</p>

<p>I am aiming to change these bad habits and achieve more balance by honestly carving out time everyday to spend being active, whether it be a hike, the gym, or a fierce game of raquetball.</p>

<p>Time has been flying by and it's time for me to start making sure I will be around for a while!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
