<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[undefined - Calvin Webster]]></title><description><![CDATA[My space for space]]></description><link>http://calweb.github.io/</link><generator>Ghost</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 21:02:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://calweb.github.io/tag/undefined/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[More of a man...]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://farm7.staticflickr.com/6112/6329588043_3ccafd063f.jpg" alt="">
It&#8217;s been close to a year that I married my best friend and the person that inspires me everyday to be a better person.
Nearly 5 years ago I packed all my stuff up and moved to Charleston to find better opportunities both for life in general and to further my career in the world of web/software development.</p>
<p>I can honestly say that on all fronts, I couldn&#8217;t be in a better position than I am now.</p>
<p>I married and became best friends with an amazing women, I have a baby on the way (less than 5wks now)&#8230;and I work at one of the best software development shops in SC.</p>
<!--more-->
<p><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7127/7771573350_41ed348f20_o.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>Personally and professionally, I&#8217;m loving life.  And with the upcoming birth of our first child, I&#8217;ve been reflecting a lot on where I&#8217;ve been and where I want to be.</p>
<p>I find that I&#8217;ve been spending a lot of time worrying about how I will be as a father and will I be able to keep the pace with the demands of a new child.  I&#8217;ve let myself go health-wise and have become &#8216;more of a man&#8217; from not paying attention to what I eat and the exercise I need to be healthy.  This, as I&#8217;m starting to realize, needs to change.</p>
<p>Changing these habits of eating and now exercising has been hard because I&#8217;ve been so unbalanced in my daily life, neglecting to really balance my personal needs.</p>
<p>I am aiming to change these bad habits and achieve more balance by honestly carving out time everyday to spend being active, whether it be a hike, the gym, or a fierce game of raquetball.</p>
<p>Time has been flying by and it&#8217;s time for me to start making sure I will be around for a while!</p>
]]></description><link>/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/08/13/more-of-a-man-dot-dot-dot.html</guid><category><![CDATA[reflection]]></category><category><![CDATA[improvement]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>