<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[undefined - Calvin Webster]]></title><description><![CDATA[My space for space]]></description><link>http://calweb.github.io/</link><generator>Ghost</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 09:00:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://calweb.github.io/tag/undefined/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Luca is almost 6 months!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<iframe width="640" height="360" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/rFbdtrl2ACY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

<p>I love a lot of things, a lot of people especially, but besides Anne Marie, I don&#8217;t know how I could love my little son more&#8230;I feel like I&#8217;m going to explode!</p>
]]></description><link>/2013/02/21/luca-is-almost-6-months.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2013/02/21/luca-is-almost-6-months.html</guid><category><![CDATA[family]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 15:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's a boy, meet Luca Alexander Webster]]></title><description><![CDATA[<iframe width="640" height="360" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Tkl44xazDYI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

<p>It&#8217;s official!  We have (well, have had now for 2 1/2 months) a beautiful baby boy named Luca Alexander Webster, weighing in at 6lbs 12oz.</p>
<p>Needless to say things have stayed busy, especially for Anne Marie, but I&#8217;m so excited to be a father and ready to fill out my new role.  In the video above, he is less than an hour old and recovering from being intubated as he was not breathing initially when he came out.</p>
<!--more-->
<p><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8066/8191478409_fdebb0feb8.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>The time has flown by!  What is really cool is that I&#8217;m finding he has a cute little personality and soooo many facial expressions. All the joys people mention when having a new little one are true, and it&#8217;s hard to describe how awesome it really is to hold your own, your little one.</p>
<p>Besides having a lot of reflux, he sleeps really well and is a playful baby. He&#8217;s not really cooing yet, but he smiles and acts like he is riding a bicycle if you lay him flat.  He defnitely will be an active child!</p>
<p>I can&#8217;t wait to start documenting more as he grows and grows.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m finding that I am thinking about things that didn&#8217;t really matter to me before like what are the nearest schools or what am I doing to be ready for when he walks&#8230;.or even what could he pull out of the walls that may hurt him.  Are there schools nearby that will be a good fit? Do we want to do Montessori?  Who will he be when he grows up?  Will he like who I am as a person?</p>
<p>I know some of that is a little silly, but still, its like my life got so much bigger (in a really good way)&#8230;and I want to make sure I make as much room and prepare as much as I can so I can allow as much growth, love, and happiness as possible.</p>
<p>The little guy is amazing and I can&#8217;t wait for all of my friends and family to meet him!</p>
<p>Here he is as a Ninja on Halloween:</p>
<p><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8463/8143704874_5b6f6c8f07.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>And his angry face when he wants to be held:</p>
<p><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8070/8198046318_87cf556c8f.jpg" alt=""></p>
]]></description><link>/2012/11/16/its-a-boy-meet-luca-alexander-webster.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">/2012/11/16/its-a-boy-meet-luca-alexander-webster.html</guid><category><![CDATA[family]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Webster]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>